沈万三你好威风呀
欺负到我头上来
我没有我没有
主上树下岂敢冒犯尊严
请主上试下
你们沈氏集团
断了我老婆乔氏集团的所有资金链
限你5分钟之内赶到总裁办
否则后果自负好好好
嗯茶也不错嗯
就是泡的差点意思
林凡赶来沈氏集团闹事
你活腻歪了你
小波你是小贝
我可以不跟你计较
现在恢复你们沈家对乔氏集团的投
资以前的事我可以不再追究
哼林凡
就凭你乔家一切坠悬
有什么资格让我恢复投资
就凭你爷爷沈万三看到我
也不敢坐着跟我说话
烫死我了
日本你知道我爷爷是谁吗
江东首富沈万三
小明二狗子
我操
这小子怎么知道我爷爷的小名
林凡范女之象
在这江东
只有别人对我沈家公义
没有人能让我沈家低头
沈二狗要是知道有你这么个孙子
至少得折寿十年
Shen Wansan, you are so majestic
Bullied me
I don't have it. I don't have it.
How dare you offend your dignity under the tree?
Please try it above.
Your Shen Group
Broke all the capital chains of my wife's Joe's Group
You are limited to arrive at the CEO's office within 5 minutes
Otherwise, you will be responsible for the consequences.
Hmm, the tea is good too
It means almost soaking.
Lin Fan came to the Shen Group to make trouble
You are tired of living
Xiaobo, you are Beckham
I can ignore you.
Now resume your Shen family's investment in Qiao's Group
I can stop pursuing the past
Hmph Lin Fan
With your Qiao family, everything is hanging in the balance
What qualifications do I have to resume my investment?
Just because your grandfather Shen Wansan saw me
Don't dare to sit and talk to me
It burned me.
Japan, do you know who my grandfather is?
Shen Wansan, the richest man in Jiangdong
Xiaoming two dogs
fuck
How did this kid know my grandfather's nickname?
Lin Fan Fan Female Elephant
Here in Jiangdong
Only others are fair to my Shen family
No one can make my Shen family bow their heads
If Shen Ergou knew you had such a grandson
At least ten years of life